1. [Champs Sports](https://help.champssports.com/hc/en-us)
2. [Privacy, Terms & Conditions](https://help.champssports.com/hc/en-us/categories/360002217533-Privacy-Terms-Conditions)
3. [Privacy Statement](https://help.champssports.com/hc/en-us/sections/360005331573-Privacy-Statement)

Articles in this section

Privacy Statement
=================

Updated June 2024

Thank you for visiting our Website or using our App or other Services. This Privacy Statement outlines the information we collect, how we may use and disclose it, and what your options are with respect to our practices. If you have any questions, please contact us at [privacyteam@footlocker.com.](mailto:privacyteam@footlocker.com)

**Privacy Statement**

Foot Locker, Inc., its subsidiaries, or its affiliates (referred to as Foot Locker, Kids Foot Locker, Champs Sports, FLX, “we,” “us,” or “our” herein) believe in protecting your information. With this in mind, we have adopted this Privacy Statement, which describes the information we may collect when you visit our websites (each a “Site”), sign up for a brand loyalty membership (each a “Membership Program”), use our mobile applications (each an “App”) shop in and visit our stores (each a “Store”) and use and/or participate in social media sites, events, promotions, digital advertising, texts, QR codes, emails and other technologies (collectively the “Services”). By using the Services, you agree to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Statement. If you do not, please do not use the Services.

This Privacy Statement addresses:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **[Notice at Collection of Personal Information](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9R56XEWBYXJDMRCTYH6WB)**  <br><br>   **** [**Option to Opt-Out from our sale or sharing of your personal              information, including targeted advertising.**](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9S9EWC2ZGWZMMED1RY2DX)  <br>  <br><br>   **** **[Categories of Personal Information We Collect](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9SSM7NDY9Y7W155QT83Y0)**  <br>  <br><br>   ** [How We Use and Retain Your Personal Information](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9T5YZBZYWD4H2WBT04ZT3)** |     |

#### **  
NOTICE AT COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “personal information” refers to information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, to you, and includes “personal data” or similar terms as defined in applicable law. We collect the categories of personal information identified below. As indicated in the chart, we “sell” or “share” some of these categories (as such terms are defined in California law) to advertising networks, data analytics providers, social networks, and data brokers for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement, including to inform you of offers, promotions, and services, and for third parties to perform services on our behalf like marketing or advertising. We do not knowingly “sell” or “share” (as such terms are defined and used in applicable privacy law) personal information of persons under the age of 16.

#### **A.         Option to Opt-Out from our sale or sharing of your personal information, including targeted advertising**:

Please click [dataprivacy.footlocker-inc.com/consumer/donotsell](https://dataprivacy.footlocker-inc.com/consumer/donotsell) to opt out of our sale or sharing of your personal information, including targeted advertising. You may also choose to enable online, where available, a universal tool that automatically communicates your opt-out preferences, such as the Global Privacy Control (“GPC”).  We will process the GPC signal as a request to opt out of sales, sharing, or targeted advertising where required by applicable law.

| #### **B.         Categories of Personal Information We Collect** (_including within the preceding 12 months_) | **Do we “sell” or “share” the category of personal information as these terms are defined in applicable privacy laws?** |
| --- | --- |
| **Identifiers/Contact Information**, including your name, postal address, zip code, email address, phone number, membership numbers, account username and credentials, device IDs, cookie IDs, and IP address. | Yes |
| **Characteristics of Protected Classifications Under California or Federal Law,** including your gender, age / date of birth, race, color, religion, ancestry, and national origin. | No  |
| **Commercial Information**, including your purchase and usage history, credit card information (for processing purchases), preferences, survey content, product reviews, and redemption information. | Yes |
| **Professional and Employment-related Information, including your employment information or household income.** | No  |
| **Internet or Other Electronic Network Activity Information, such as your web/app browsing and search history through our Services, and information related to your online interaction(s) with the Services, emails, texts or our advertising.** | Yes |
| **Geolocation Data, including automatic collection of  geolocation data through your use of the Services.** | Yes |
| **Education Information, such as educational level.** | No  |
| **Inferences**, meaning inferences that we draw from your information and web activity to help create a personalized profile so we can better identify goods and services that may be of interest. | Yes |
| **Sensitive Personal Information, including your racial and ethnic origin, precise geo-location data, religion and to the extent deemed sensitive data your log-in credentials to your account.** | No  |

#### **C.         How We Use and Retain Your Personal Information**

We may use the information we collect from and about you for the following business purposes:

1.         To provide you with a quick and simple checkout experience;

2.         To process your orders, contact you concerning the status of an order, answer any of your questions, or otherwise contact and communicate with you;

3.         To address problems with the Services, our business or our products and services, and to protect the security of the Site and our business; and

4.         To help us learn more about our Site and Store visitors, App and Service users, Membership Program members, and customers and to improve their shopping experience and our business.

We may also use the information we collect from and about you for the following commercial purposes:

1.         To provide you with customized content, targeted offers, and advertising on the Services, other websites or via text message, and to contact you about upcoming Foot Locker sales, promotions, and product information;

2.         To allow you to participate in promotions; and

3.         To contact you about upcoming promotions and offers on behalf of our partners.

We may also use the information we collect from and about you for other purposes that we explain to you when we collect your information and as otherwise permitted by law.

We will retain personal information for as long as reasonably needed or permitted in light of the purpose(s) for which it was obtained. The criteria used to determine our retention periods include: (i) the length of time we have an ongoing relationship with you; (ii) whether there is a legal obligation to which we are subject; (iii) whether there is a privacy right for which the personal information has been exercised (such as a request to delete); and (iv) whether retention is advisable in light of our legal position (such as in regard to applicable statutes of limitations, litigation or regulatory investigations).

#### **Information Collection**

**1.  Information You Provide to Us**

We collect personal information as listed in the above Notice at Collection from you when you provide it to us, such as when you: (1) register/create an account; (2) purchase one of our products or services or redeem FLX Membership Points; (3) complete a survey or product review; (4) participate in one of our promotions, contests, sweepstakes; (5) sign up for a Membership Program, newsletter or other communication; or (6) contact us. If you use a third-party login (such as a social network) to register or otherwise link to us, we may receive certain information about you from the third party based on your registration and privacy settings on that third-party service.

**2.  Registration/Create an Account**

We encourage you to register/create an account when shopping on our Site or App; however, registration is not required. Our [Registration Form](https://www.footlocker.com/account/create) may require users to provide contact information (such as name, date of birth, zip code, mailing address, daytime telephone number, cell phone number, gender, e-mail address, and password). You must be 13 years of age or older to register. Registration helps us to provide you with a quick and simple checkout experience and administer the Membership Program if you register for a Membership Program.  The customer contact information you provide will be used to contact you concerning the status of an order, answer your questions and, unless you choose to opt-out, to send you communications about upcoming sales, contests, promotions, advertising and product information. You acknowledge and agree that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your registration information and password. You are responsible for all use of the Site or App and other Services under your registered account. If you would like, you can also fill out a customer profile. While it is not required, information obtained from your registration and the customer profile helps us to learn more about our customers and is used to improve your shopping experience and to provide you with more relevant content and advertising.

**3.  Information We Automatically Collect**

We and our service providers and other third parties may use cookies, beacons, pixel tags, log files, or other technologies to automatically collect certain information when you use our Site, App, Membership Program, Store or other Services or interact with our emails or advertisements on our Site, our App, Membership Program, Store or other websites or services. A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. The information that we and our providers and other third parties collect through cookies and other technologies, along with information that we share with them, enables us or our providers to recognize you or your device and to serve ads to you or your device. For example, these technologies may allow us to automatically collect information such as your IP address, geolocation data, unique user ID, Device ID, Mobile Ad Identifiers, browser type and version, character set, screen size and color, language, cell phone model, operating system and version, carrier, and Internet Service Provider. This information: (1) allows us to accurately and properly pay for ads placed on our behalf (e.g., an ad that led you to purchase or download one of our products) and get paid when you see an ad on  or about our Services; (2) helps prevent you from repeatedly seeing the same ads; (3) helps select and display targeted ads or other content on your computer or device (such as on a site or social networking service you are visiting or a mobile application you are using) that may be of interest to you; and (4) helps us measure and analyze interactions with our ads and Services. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services. This site uses cookies and other technologies to also help keep track of items you put in your shopping cart including when you have abandoned your cart and this information is used to determine when to send cart reminder messages via SMS.

We and our service providers and other third parties also may collect information about your use of our Services, such as the time you spend using the Site or App or other Services, the number of times you return, whether you click-through, open, or forward links, e-mails, texts and ads, and other Service usage data. These technologies, such as cookies, also allow us to keep track of your order as you shop on our Site or App, to make our Site better, to enable our Services to function, to maintain your preferences and settings, to provide enhanced features, to combat fraud, to recognize registered users when they visit, and to provide registered users with information and advertising that is more relevant to them.

If you register with or order from us, we may also use cookies or other technologies to monitor and maintain information about how you use our Services and what you buy. If you do not register with or buy from us, we may also monitor and maintain information about your use in order to improve your shopping experience and provide you with more relevant content, products, Services and advertising.

#### **4.   Tracking Options**

You may adjust your browser settings to limit certain tracking or to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Services or take full advantage of our offerings. Even without a cookie, you can still take advantage of most of the features of our Site, including making a purchase, but we may not be able to recognize you as a registered user unless you log in. We may use certain service providers and others to provide you with more relevant online advertising based on your activities on our Site and third-party sites. Some of these companies are members of the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA). To learn more about the DAA and its participating companies and to opt-out of receiving from such companies interest-based advertising, as defined by the DAA, please [click here.](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN) Note, you may still receive other types of online advertising from participating companies, and these companies may still collect information for other purposes consistent with DAA Principles. We may also use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with advertising tailored to your interests.  
  
To opt-out of target marketing cookies placed on your browser when you visit our Site please click [dataprivacy.footlocker-inc.com/consumer/donotsell](https://dataprivacy.footlocker-inc.com/consumer/donotsell) and see the [Use and Management of Cookies](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9VP7BD0CWTY8VG0X40PW6)  [](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01GXXRYCFXV736V0NMDZ7PKQ7E)section below for more information. For certain service providers, such as social media platforms, and on your mobile device, you can adjust your privacy and advertising settings to limit your tracking for advertising or to control whether you receive more relevant advertising. To learn more about certain mobile and browser privacy and advertising controls see [Use and Management of Cookies](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9VP7BD0CWTY8VG0X40PW6) section below.

**5.   Information Collected From Other Sources**

We may obtain information about you from other sources, including social networks, that you use to connect with us, advertising networks, internet service providers, data analytics providers, government entities, operating systems and platforms and data brokers. This information includes, for example, your name, username, demographic information, updated address or contact information, interests, and publicly observed data, such as from social media and online activity.

**6.   Combination of Information**

We may also combine the information we receive from and about you, including the information you provide to us on the Services or through the Membership Program, information we receive from third parties, the information we automatically collect (as explained above), and information provided or collected offline such as when you shop in our Stores.

**7.   Additional Information**

For additional information on our data collection practices, please see the section [Your Privacy Rights](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9YGVTVN66N81QCGZJ6NW9) of this Privacy Statement.  For IOS device users, please also see our App privacy disclosures on the App store incorporated herein by reference.

#### **Information Disclosure**

We may disclose the information we collect from and about you as follows:

1.   Among the Foot Locker, Inc. family of companies including Foot Locker, Kids Foot Locker, Champs Sports, FLX, WSS, Atmos and our other affiliates and brands.

2.   To our service providers, if the disclosure will enable them to perform a business, professional, or technical support function for us.

3.   To carefully-selected third party partners, so that they may inform you of offers, promotions, and services; advertising networks, social networks, data analytics providers, and data brokers.

4.   For payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, customer support, Site, App and Service evaluation and optimization, and data analysis, and distributing marketing and promotional material.

5.   To comply with the law, to respond to governmental inquiries or requests, to enforce our policies, or to protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety.

6.   Otherwise, with your consent or other lawful basis.

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily upload or submit for public posting to the Services becomes publicly available and others may collect and use that information. Posting any content on the Services that requests personal information from others violates the Services’ [Terms of Use](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034292814-Terms-of-Use-Comprehensive).

As with any business, as our business develops, we may sell or buy stores, companies or other assets. In such transactions, information about customers often is among the transferred assets. Accordingly, in the event that a third party acquires our company or substantially all of our assets, such information may be one of the transferred assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personal information provided through the Services in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement.

In addition to sharing personal information, we and third parties may share aggregate or de-identified information, including about Site, App, and Service users with other third parties.  

We may share opt-in consent with Blue Core or other SMS/MMS messaging providers or other message controllers, affiliated third parties, successors in interest and others, however we may not share our messaging short code together with opt-in consent to unaffiliated third parties for the purpose of enabling such unaffiliated third parties to send marketing SMS/MMS communications to you through our short code solely on their own behalf.

**Categories of Personal Information Disclosed**: 

In the last 12 months (from the Last Updated date listed at the top of this Privacy Statement), Foot Locker has disclosed the following categories of personal information for a business purpose to support the ways in which Foot Locker uses personal information described above under “[Notice at Collection of Personal Information”](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9R56XEWBYXJDMRCTYH6WB) (such as with our service providers, to enable them to perform business, professional, or technical support functions for us and who are restricted from using your personal information outside the scope of their services to us):  Identifiers/Contact Information, Characteristics of Protected Classifications Under California or Federal Law, Professional and Employment-related Information, Education Information, Commercial Information, Internet or Other Electronic Network Activity Information, Geolocation Data, Inferences about you, and Sensitive Personal Information .

Additional information on our data disclosure practices can be found in the [Your Privacy Rights](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9YGVTVN66N81QCGZJ6NW9) Section of this Privacy Statement.

#### **Use and Management of Cookies**

We may use cookies and other technologies like them to make our site better.

You can read about how we use cookies and how you can limit or decline them in the “[Information Collection](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9TS30Z8W3YQSG783AMW7D)” Section, specifically in subsections entitled [Information We Automatically Collect](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9TS30Z8W3YQSG783AMW7D) and [Tracking Options](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1GAFV4XSSWYG61J94B50A6N)**.**

You can manage your cookies related to certain **Interest Based Advertising** through various tools, including:

1.   Adjusting your privacy and advertising settings on your mobile device (where your mobile device permits this) to control whether you receive interest-based targeted advertising. Learn more at [networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices](https://thenai.org/opt-out/mobile-opt-out/).

2.   Managing cookies or other privacy preferences using your browser settings (where available).

Please note that you may need to manage these settings for each device and browser that you use to access our website.

#### **Updating Your Information**

Please note that at all times, you are responsible for updating the personal information you provide to us. If you have registered with us or if you participate in a Membership Program, you may update your personal information through your registered account or Membership Program account. If you elect to delete some or all of your personal information, keep in mind that we may retain transactional, Membership Program-related and other data in accordance with various laws, regulations and Foot Locker’s lawful retention policies.

#### **Changes To Our Privacy Statement**

We reserve the right, at any time and in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, remove, or otherwise revise portions of this Privacy Statement.  When we update our Privacy Statement, we will take appropriate measures to inform you via the contact information we have on file or via our Site consistent with the significance of the changes we make, and in accordance with applicable law.  Except where prohibited by law, your continued use of the Site after we post changes to this Privacy Statement means you accept these changes.

**Option To Opt-Out from Marketing Communications**

At all times, you have the option of “opting out” of receiving future e-mail marketing updates by sending us an e-mail with “unsubscribe” in the subject line at [customercare@footlocker.com](mailto:customercare@footlocker.com).

Even if you opt-out, you may continue to receive non-marketing e-mail messages from us, including, for example, order confirmations.

If you previously registered for a text messaging campaign and now want to opt-out, text “STOP” to the shortcode/number for the program that you have signed up for.

#### **Children’s Privacy**

We do not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children’s products for purchase by adults. We do not direct the Site or App to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of 13.  
  
You must be 13 years of age or older to submit personal information to us, including to register or place an order on the Site or App or participate in one of our online promotions. We do not knowingly “sell” or “share” (as such terms are defined and used in applicable privacy law) personal information of persons under the age of 18. 

Please see our [**Terms of Use**](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034292814-Terms-of-Use-Comprehensive) or additional information regarding the use of these Services.

#### **Security of Information**

We have implemented a variety of physical, administrative, and technical security measures designed to help protect and help limit access to the confidentiality of your personal information under our control. We also enable encryption technology in certain circumstances to help protect certain personal information, including your credit card number.

We are committed to protecting your information, but no website, App, or system is completely safe from cyber-attacks. We need your help! Help keep your data safe by creating a unique, strong password and protect against unauthorized access to that password and your device. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared device and do not share your password with anyone.

#### **Your Privacy Rights**

**_Explanation of Applicable Privacy Rights_**

Depending on your U.S. state of residence, you may have certain rights in relation to your personal information, including:

      **Right to Know:** You may have the right to know what personal information we have collected about you, including the categories of personal information, the categories of sources from which the personal information is collected, the business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing personal information, the categories of third parties to whom we disclose personal information (including the names of such third parties), and the specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you. You may have the right to access your personal information in a portable format, all subject to appropriate verification.

      **Right to Delete:** You may have the right to delete personal information that we have collected from or about you. Note that there are some reasons when we will not be able to fully address your request, such as, where permitted, if we need to complete a transaction for you, to detect and protect against fraudulent and illegal activity, to maintain for internal purposes, or to comply with a legal obligation or to exercise our rights.

      **Right to Correct:** You may have the right to correct inaccurate personal information that we may maintain about you, subject to appropriate verification.

      **Right to Opt-Out of the Sale or Sharing of Personal Information:** You may have the right to opt-out of the “sale” or “sharing” of your personal information, as such terms are defined in applicable privacy laws, to third parties.

      **Right to Opt-Out of Targeted Advertising:** You may have the right to opt-out of targeted advertising, as such term is defined under applicable law. Opting out does not mean that we will stop non-targeted advertising.

      **Right to Appeal:** You may have the right to appeal a decision we have made in connection with your privacy rights request.

      **Right to Limit the Use or Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information:** You may have the right to limit the use or disclosure of sensitive personal information for business purposes.

      **Right to Non-Discrimination:** You may have a right not to receive discriminatory treatment by Foot Locker for exercising your privacy rights listed in this section.

**_How to Submit a Request_**

To take advantage of the privacy rights available to you based on your state of residence, please submit your request at **1-800-442-4059** or [dataprivacy.footlocker-inc.com/consumer/make\_request](https://dataprivacy.footlocker-inc.com/consumer/make_request)

or visit the [Questions/Contacting Us](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9Z8EXV55FCMHAVN9PR040) section below for additional information on how to contact us. Before we can respond to your know, correction, and deletion requests, we may ask you a series of questions in order to attempt to verify your identity. We will endeavor to respond to your request within the earlier of the period (a) required by law or (b) forty-five (45) days of receiving your request or notify you that we need additional time to process your information.

To make a request to opt out of the sale or sharing of personal information, or to opt out of targeted advertising, you or your authorized agent may click on the [dataprivacy.footlocker-inc.com/consumer/donotsell or](https://dataprivacy.footlocker-inc.com/consumer/donotsell) the Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information link, which is also on our website footer (“Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information”), or contact us by calling **1-800-442-4059.** **You may also choose to enable online, where available, a universal tool that automatically communicates your opt-out preferences, such as the** [Global Privacy Control (“GPC”)](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/)**.  We will process the GPC signal as a request to opt-out of targeted advertising or the sale or sharing of your personal information where required by applicable law, or if not required, at our discretion.** 

For more information on managing cookies used for advertising purposes, see the Section above entitled [Use and Management of Cookies](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9VP7BD0CWTY8VG0X40PW6) and **Interest Based Advertising**. Please note that if, after opting out, you submit a deletion request or change the Personal Information that you share with us, you may be required to submit a subsequent opt-out request.

**_Agent Requests_**

You may authorize someone to make a privacy rights request on your behalf (an authorized agent). Authorized agents will need to demonstrate that you’ve authorized them to act on your behalf or must demonstrate they have power of attorney pursuant to applicable probate law. Foot Locker retains the right to request confirmation directly from you confirming that the agent is authorized to make such a request, or to request additional information to confirm the agent’s identity. An authorized agent is prohibited from using a consumer’s personal information, or any information collected from or about the consumer, for any purpose other than to fulfill the consumer’s requests, for verification, or for fraud prevention. 

**_Use and Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information_**

To the extent that we collect, use, or share “sensitive personal information” as that term is defined in applicable California law for other than permitted business purposes, we offer a Right to Limit the Use or Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information as required by California law.

To the extent that we collect, use, or share “sensitive data” or “sensitive personal information” as that term is defined in applicable law, we endeavor to process it per your consent.

**_Affiliate Disclosures_**_._

Foot Locker may share your personal information with some or all brands in the Foot Locker, Inc. family of companies, some of which do not share the “Foot Locker” name, for their direct marketing purposes. California law considers these affiliates to be unaffiliated parties. If you are a California resident, you may request certain information regarding how we disclose personal information to these Foot Locker family brands for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us as directed below.

#### **Notice of Financial Incentive**

Foot Locker offers the FLX Program, a loyalty program through which you can earn points and later redeem them for offers, products, services, events, and other rewards. Membership in the FLX Program is free of charge. [Click here](https://www.footlocker.com/flx.html) to learn more about the FLX Program and to create an account. The FLX Membership Terms and Conditions are available [here.](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360042738733-What-are-the-full-FLX-Program-membership-terms-and-conditions) After you join, you can deactivate your account at any time by calling Customer Service at 800.991.6883.

We collect personal information in connection with the FLX Program in order to run the FLX Program, and as otherwise described in this Privacy Statement, including your first and last name, date of birth, zip code, gender, and email address.  Because we collect personal information, this may be interpreted as a “financial incentive” program under California law or a “bona fide loyalty program” under Colorado law. Foot Locker uses and may disclose this information for the purpose described above under [“Notice at Collection of Personal Information.”](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9R56XEWBYXJDMRCTYH6WB) The value of your personal information that we collect in connection with the FLX Program is reasonably related to the expenses related to the discounts and other perks that we offer to FLX Program members.

Foot Locker may also offer promotions or discounts when you provide your contact information and enroll to receive direct marketing messages.  We collect personal information in connection with these promotions or discounts as described in the section entitled [Information Collection](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9TS30Z8W3YQSG783AMW7D)

for purposes described above under “[Notice at Collection of Personal Information](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9R56XEWBYXJDMRCTYH6WB)”,  including your name, email address, or phone number. Because we collect personal information, this may be interpreted as a “financial incentive” program under California law or a “bona fide loyalty program” under Colorado law.  Foot Locker uses and may disclose this information for the purposes described above under [“Notice at Collection of Personal Information](https://help.footlocker.com/hc/en-us/articles/360034125214#h_01J1G9R56XEWBYXJDMRCTYH6WB).”

The complete terms of the promotion or discount are provided when you enroll to receive direct marketing messages. You may un-enroll in direct marketing messages at any time by clicking “unsubscribe” in email marketing or replying “Stop” to text message marketing. If you ask us to delete your personal information, we will not be able to provide you with access to the benefits associated with such direct marketing messages.

The value of your personal information that we collect in connection with these discounts and promotions is reasonably related to the expenses we incur related to fulfilling the discounts that we offer when you enroll.

#### **Questions/Contacting Us**

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement generally or our data handling practices specifically, you may contact us as follows:

Attn:  Privacy Team (Law Department)  
Foot Locker Inc.  
330 W. 34th St.  
4th Floor  
New York, NY 10001  

#### **Links To Other Websites**

These Services contain links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites or apps. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the Privacy Statement posted on any website or app that you access through the Services. The terms and conditions herein do not apply to any such linked websites or apps. Foot Locker does not endorse any linked websites or apps, or the information, materials, products or services that linked websites or apps contain or make accessible. Foot Locker disclaims all warranties, express or implied, with respect to the information, materials, products, and services that linked websites or apps contain or make accessible, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose or non-infringement.

You acknowledge and agree that Foot Locker is not responsible for the content, accuracy, legality, decency, copyright compliance, privacy practices, security or any other aspects of any such linked websites or apps. You further acknowledge and agree that your access or use of any such linked websites or apps is solely at your own risk, and you hereby waive any and all claims against Foot Locker with respect to such linked websites or apps.

#### **Data Transfers**

We may transfer the personal information we collect about you through our Services to countries other than the country in which we collect the information. If you are an international visitor using our Services, please be aware that we may transfer the information you provide to computers in the United States. We take steps to ensure that we process the data collected under this Privacy Statement according to the purposes set out in this Privacy Statement and, in transferring data, that we protect the information as described herein.

**Data Privacy Framework Policy**  
  
We participate in the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework, the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework, and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework for data received in the United States from the European Union, Switzerland, or the United Kingdom.

For more information access our [Data Privacy Framework Policy.](https://www.footlocker-inc.com/content/flinc-aem-site/en/data-privacy-framework.html)

Was this article helpful?

Yes No

Related articles
----------------

* Foot Locker Inc, 330 W. 34th St., New York, NY 10001 | [800-991-6813](tel:"800-991-6813") | [Contact Us](https://help.champssports.com/hc/en-us/articles/360047275753-Contact-Us)
